THABO ELDRIDGE SODI

PROFILE

I am a very committed, adaptable, and dedicated individual with knowledge in Web App development and Database design. I am aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the software developer role. I have worked on projects using SQL programming, Angular, Ionic, NodeJS, Figma, Trello and PostgreSQL.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Phone : +27 64 723 6678

Email :

thabosodi11@gmail.com

Residential address:

Alberton 1448

EDUCATION

Modubatse High School 2010 - 2014 National Senior Certificate - Bachelor

Tshwane University of Technology 2015 -

National Diploma – Information Technology (Software Development)

Certificates

Microsoft AZ – 900 Azure fundamentals Microsoft 98 – 361 Software development fundamentals Udemy MySQL Development Udemy Ethical hacking Udemy Web development bootcamp(current)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Blue Gill import

Kempton Park, Nov 2017 – Feb 2018

Dynamic DNA

Randburg, April 2021 – June 2021

Digital Academy

Auckland park, Jan 2022 – Nov 2022

SKILLS

HTML & CSS figma GIT SQL Docker

REFERENCE

Sandy Macaulay (Dynamic DNA Talent Manager)

e-mail: smacaulay@dynamicdna.co.za

Tel: 011 759 5940